Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/rama-peetla-02986032 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

OBIEE

OBIA

Informatica

Languages

English

Hindi (Limited Working)

Telugu

Rama Peetla

Data Engineer |ETL| Data Warehouse |ODI | Informatica | Snap Logic | OBI | Tableau | Power BI | BiApps | Cloud | Analytics | Data Analyst

Dallas-Fort Worth Metroplex

Summary

Having 15 Years experience in Implementing several SDLC for various clients from Scratch and out of the box(Vanilla Implementations) along with client preferred Customization Worked on Following Techno-Function area along with different technologies and tools.

Financial ,Retail,Banking,Manafature,Siebel CRM,POS,Procurement & Spend ,Order Management,Transportation ,Heath Care and Student Information.

Expertise Area's
OBIEE/Tableau/OACS/POWER BI
OBIA/EBS/CRM/POS
ODI/Informatica/ETL/Snaplogic
DAC/Auto Sys
Oracle/Sql Server/Snowflake
Cloud Technologies

Experience

Verizon

Sr Bl/ ETL/Data Analyst May 2019 - Present (4 years)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Working on Different databases for analysis and writing complex etl to build data visualization reports using Power BI & Tableau reports for SLT teams.. Building 5G network enabling through intelligent edge network

Lands' End Business Intelligence Architect December 2018 - May 2019 (6 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Worked on Financial and Procurement Spend Analytics.

Implementing Warehouse for EBS source ..

Mazda North American Operations Sr BI/ETI Developer July 2018 - December 2018 (6 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Designed Competitor sales reporting system ,worked on Vehicle Recalls Dashboard ..

Los Angeles Metro **BI** Architect April 2018 - June 2018 (3 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Installed configured 11g to 12c Integrated legacy data to edw Creating data mashups using obi 12c

Aramark Uniform Services Sr BI Developer/ETL August 2016 - March 2018 (1 year 8 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Working on Bi Apps 11.1.1.7 (EBS 12.1.3) with ODI, implementing Service module and financials . SSRS reporting on field management area ..

Riot Games OBIA Techno Functional Architect March 2016 - August 2016 (6 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Implementing entire OBIA Financial Analytic's (11.1.1.10) on EBS 12.2.4 source for Rapid Deployment with limited time.

Hyundai Motor America ETL Lead October 2015 - March 2016 (6 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Worked on SAP SUCCESS FACTORS in order to bring Master Dealer and Student Course modules into ODS & EDW Environment with help of ETL tool ,for supporting other down stream Systems ..

L.A. Care Health Plan Sr BI Developer/ETL Developer October 2014 - September 2015 (1 year)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Worked on Heath Care Analytic's, Encouter's Data for Plan partners related DHS of CA.

Schnitzer Steel
POS/ODI-OBIEE Specalist
July 2014 - October 2014 (4 months)
Portland, Oregon Metropolitan Area

Worked on POS-OBIEE Conversion Projects using ODI..

The Nature's Bounty Co.
ODI-OBIEE/ORDM Lead
April 2014 - July 2014 (4 months)
Long Island, Newyork

Worked on Retail Domain Modules -ORDM- for Entire Implementation.Retail Analytic's..

Fidelity Investments
Sr OBIEE/ETL Developer
December 2012 - March 2014 (1 year 4 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Extensively worked on Procurement and Spend Analytic's ,Order Managment ,VMIS and Risk Management Area's for financial and Investment data.

Cummins Inc.
BI Tech Lead
July 2012 - December 2012 (6 months)
Columbus,Indiana

Worked on Manufacture Analytic's, EDS Analytic's, Bolts R12 and participated in Siebel Integration for CRM modules

Conagra Brands
OBIEE Developer
November 2011 - June 2012 (8 months)
Omaha, Nebraska

Worked on OTM 6.1 Module Along with FTI Reports for load planner and score cards with SAP Source DB

JPMorgan Chase & Co.

Report Developer June 2011 - October 2011 (5 months) Columbus, Ohio Metropolitan Area

Worked on Mortgage System and Banking Domains with Financial Data

International Technological University (ITU)
System Analyst
December 2010 - May 2011 (6 months)
Sanjose, California

Gowtham model school Computer Programmer July 2006 - July 2007 (1 year 1 month) Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Acharya Nagarjuna University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Mathematics and Computer Science

International Technological University (ITU)

Master of Science - MS, Computer Engineering